Obasi Kennedy Ositadimma

Software Engineer

0

22 ilupeju, Magboro, Ogun

kenosssyobasi@gmail.com

+2348140817343

in

kennedy-obasi

Profile

I have over a year of experience building software web applications. My Experience cuts across different languages like JavaScript, TypeScript, React and Next.Js, used in building well-designed and highly scalable web and also different UI libraries for the styling.

Professional Experience

11/2023 – 08/2024 Lagos, Nigeria

Prunedge Limited, Software Trainee Intern

- Actively sought opportunities to improve coding skills by attending workshops and training sessions
- Contributed to a 20% reduction in development time by collaborating with a team of developers in the development and maintenance of software application.
- Utilized version control tools such as Git for effective collaboration among team members.
- Supported team members in troubleshooting complex issues, fostering a collaboration among team members.
- Mentored some of my fellow Interns.

10/2024 – Present Lagos, Nigeria

Auxano Solutions Technology Limited, Frontend Developer

- Designed and Implemented web application as a web team for all interdepartment and customer facing-projects.
- Work closely with programmers and clients to meet project requirements, goals and desired functionality.
- Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.

Skills

| React | HTML/CSS | JavaScript |
|--------------|-------------|-------------|
| Tailwind-CSS | Typescript | React Query |
| Shadcn-UI | Material-UI | Next.JS |

Tanstack Query

Education

09/2018- 09/2023

Enugu State University of Science and Technology

Enugu, Nigeria

Anatomy

Projects

Chat App

This is a web application for interactions between people built with React, TypeScript and Material-UI. [5]

GitHub Link - https://github.com/Kimo08/raxs.git

Klexo Banking App

This is a modern banking application built with Next.Js, TypeScript, Shadon-ui with Appwrite for the API implementation and Sentry for the protection of the banking system.

GitHub Link - https://github.com/Kimo08/km banking.git

Movie App

This is a software application that allows users to view their favourite shows, latest movies and other movies with the mobile phones and laptops which was built with Next.Js, TypeScript, Tailwind-CSS and API code from IMDb .

GitHub Link – https://github.com/Kimo08/movie_next.git